by RentAnAdviser.com
Obie Trice! Real name, no gimmicks
(*record scratch*)
Two trailer park girls
go 'round the outside
'Round the outside, 'round the outside
Two trailer park girls
go 'round the outside
'Round the outside, 'round the outside
Guess who's back, back again
Shady's back, tell a friend
Guess who's back, guess who's back
Guess who's back
I've created a monster,
'cause nobody wants to
See Marshall no more, they want
Shady, I'm chopped liver
Well, if you want Shady, this
is what I'll give ya
A little bit of weed mixed
with some hard liquor
Some vodka that'll jump
start my heart quicker
Than a shock when I get shocked
at the hospital
By the doctor when I'm
not co-operating
When I'm rocking the table while
he's operating (Hey!)
You waited this long,
now stop debating
'Cause I'm back, I'm on
the rag and ovulating
I know that you got a job, Ms. Cheney
But your husband's heart
problem's complicating
So the FCC won't let me be
Or let me be me, so let me see
They try to shut me down on MTV
But it feels so empty without me
So, come on and dip, bum on your lips
Fuck that! Cum on your lips
and some on your tits
And get ready, 'cause this
shit's about to get heavy
I just settled all my lawsuits,
fuck you, Debbie!
Now this looks like a job for me
So everybody, just follow me
'Cause we need a little controversy
'Cause it feels so empty without me
I said this looks like a job for me
So everybody, just follow me
'Cause we need a little controversy
'Cause it feels so empty without me
Little hellions, kids
feeling rebellious
Embarrassed their parents
still listen to Elvis
They start feeling like
prisoners helpless
'Til someone comes along on a
mission and yells, "Bitch!"
A visionary, vision is scary
Could start a revolution,
polluting the airwaves
A rebel, so just let me revel and bask
In the fact that I got everyone
kissing my ass (*smack*)
And it's a disaster,
such a catastrophe
For you to see so damn much of
my ass—you asked for me?
Well, I'm back, na-na-na-
na-na-na-na-na-na-na
Fix your bent antenna, tune
it in, and then I'm gonna
Enter in, and up under your
skin like a splinter
The center of attention,
back for the winter
I'm interesting, the best
thing since wrestling
Infesting in your kid's
ears and nesting
Testing, "Attention please"
Feel the tension soon as
someone mentions me
Here's my ten cents, my
two cents is free
A nuisance, who sent? You sent for me?
Now this looks like a job for me
So everybody, just follow me
'Cause we need a little controversy
'Cause it feels so empty without me
I said this looks like a job for me
So everybody, just follow me
'Cause we need a little controversy
'Cause it feels so empty without me
A tisk-it a task-it, I'll
go tit for tat with
Anybody who's talking "This
shit, that shit"
Chris Kirkpatrick, you can
get your ass kicked
Worse than them little
Limp Bizkit bastards
And Moby? You can get stomped by Obie
You thirty-six-year-old baldheaded
fag, blow me
You don't know me, you're
too old, let go
It's over, nobody listens to techno
Now let's go, just give me the signal
I'll be there with a whole
list full of new insults
I've been dope, suspenseful
with a pencil
Ever since Prince turned
himself into a symbol
But sometimes the shit just seems
Everybody only wants to discuss me
So this must mean I'm disgusting
But it's just me, I'm just obscene
Though I'm not the first
king of controversy
I am the worst thing
since Elvis Presley
To do black music so selfishly
And use it to get myself
wealthy (Hey!)
There's a concept that works
Twenty million other white
rappers emerge
But no matter how many fish in the sea
It'd be so empty without me
Now this looks like a job for me
So everybody, just follow me
'Cause we need a little controversy
'Cause it feels so empty without me
I said this looks like a job for me
So everybody, just follow me
'Cause we need a little controversy
'Cause it feels so empty without me
Hum dei dei la la, la la la la la
La la la la la, la la la la
Kids!
by RentAnAdviser.com